You're here at the right time
That's him
CEO Cha Jin-hee
Please choose your own
Elijah!
Oh my, congratulations, congratulations, ayu!
congratulations, congratulations
Elijah's biological mother
I reported it directly.
Do you even know?
I'm very just
Because of that, Ma Young-sook
Just how boiled my insides were...
How did you get on the schedule?
You should come, uh, aren't you coming?
Like this today
I heard some good news?
It's getting a little confusing, isn't it?
- Let’s say hello.
- Yeah, I guess so?
yes
Thank you, lawyer.
Yes, yes, yes
Thank you for your hard work, yes
no
Ah, yes, yes
I've been a bit rude all these years, right?
yes sorry
shamefully
It's a bit like a mother's heart.
It's my baby's business
It feels a little distant before my eyes
I can't see anything
yes, sorry
no
I fully understand
What is a mother's heart?
That's it.
thank you
mom
Pro bono lawyers here
Thank you for your hard work.
Ah, yes
Oh my, thank you for your hard work
- Oh, no.
- Yes
Ah, the hardest
Comments IP Tracking
Attorney Jang
I did it all night long.
Uh, really? Earlier…
Ah, thank you
Oh no, yeah
Yeah, it's no big deal, whatever.
- Ah, bro, that
- Yes
Jihye said she was a huge fan of Elijah.
Tell me quickly
Hey, please at least give me an autograph.
And me too...
Sign?
Ah, these days I
There is someone I am consulting with.
Elijah is a huge fan.
If you could at least give me an autograph
I think you'll really like it, yeah
The lawyer
If you are helping
He must be a very difficult person.
Oh, please come with me sometime.
I will meet you in person and sign it for you.
- Huh?
- Ma, Ma, you’re meeting me?
yes
Jihye would really like it.
Oh, thank you, Elijah.
Well, let us
I have some schedules.
Let's go first.
- Oh, yes.
- Yes, yes.
Yes, ah, you guys really.
Reversal charm, perfect
Oh, yes, let's go.
yes, yes
Thank you!
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Come in!
under…
Is it really true?
What happened to my biological mother?
You mean that?
What does that mean?
What is your biological mother?
My ears are bright too
Does that make sense?
Your mom reported that?
yes?
I don't really have the motivation to do that.
No, before I was a mother.
He's the CEO of the agency, huh?
What do you need to get?
In my sense
Koo Ji-hwan is probably right.
Yes? why?
that human
All kinds of things in the entertainment industry
I was only asked to do dirty work
It's famous for making a living.
CEO Cha
Maybe I commissioned something
Oh, no way
Are you family?
no, how
Would a parent do that to their child?
family
It could be the cruelest
No, my brother
Why are you being so negative?
huh?
Oh, just…
Ah, the one I’m in charge of these days.
I guess it’s because of Ji-hye’s incident.
Oh, well, anyway
We won today, huh?
Because today was Yoo Nanhee’s solo stage.
Nanhee will shoot
- ok
- What?
Why do you do that...
I'll shoot!
Because I'm not a bandit!
So, eat as much as you want today, ta-da!
-Ha
- Ta-da!
I'm a bandang
“O&Partners”
Huh?
why?
This
Isn’t Elijah your boyfriend?
why? what?
What is it, what is it?
Is this kid crazy?
This is mine
Mine, mine...
Wow, holy crap! seed…
Who is trash?
Lawyer Kang
What?
Let’s go to CEO Cha Jin-hee right away.
- Huh?
- I think I understand.
CEO Cha Jin-hee
What did you request from Koo Ji-hwan?
Are you saying that now?
Ah, this
Why, why can’t I empathize?
Hey, when I wrote this song
Did you know that the lyrics just came out?
It's nothing else
I just made a mistake while working.
While working!
Let's just move on.
Shut up, you piece of trash.
Are you okay?
under…
Yeah, it's okay
But
Now in the CEO’s room
Those lawyers are here.
Huh?
why?
Please sit this way.
Ah…
First of all, I would like to say this
I don't know if you'll believe it, but
Regarding the issue of my mother and children,
I can't be objective
I'm always on mom's side unconditionally.
Yes, why are you suddenly saying that?
Why did you do that?
What are you talking about?
You reported it, right?
About Elijah’s boyfriend
Ah, on what basis?
Is that what you are saying?
Oh, I'm a little embarrassed.
I wrote an article about the burst leg of lamb today.
internet media
That
Attorney Koo Ji-hwan
I heard it was operated under a different name.
CEO
That lawyer
Do you know what kind of person he is?
He's a lawyer
By exposing the weaknesses of others and threatening them
I am a person who makes a living.
People like that
I don't care about customer protection or anything like that.
Because I'm getting desperate
You came first and had a blast?
You're my mom.
How can you let someone like that handle your daughter’s business…?
Because I'm a mom
Yes?
I do it for my baby
I'll do worse than that.
Mom said that?
Let's go out and talk
go out and talk
It's my private life
Did your mom really say that? why?
Why on earth?
Did you want to ruin me?
no!
Why would I do that!
No, I just
That bastard, ugh.
Drop it...
No, I trust you mom.
Mom did that for you
Ah...
no, please
I'm afraid you'll do something wrong
So please
Looking after others
They are humans
Such people
Don't you know what kind of people they are?
I also received money from the CEO.
Elijah, I leaked that he was your boyfriend.
I also made a business out of the number of views.
I guess I was crazy
No matter how I look at it, it doesn't seem like it
Our Elijah
Because I keep being stubborn
My child makes mistakes
Mom opens both eyes
How can you watch?
uh?
That's right
That kid is trash.
Now you know, right?
But
That trash is the trash I chose.
No…
Even if I throw it away
I should have thrown it away
Huh, Elijah
Mom did that for you.
only us
I did it for my pretty daughter!
under…
I'm sick of it now, Mom.
Ha…
Elijah
ah… What should I do?
Ah…
Elijah!
Wow
Ha, calm down.
Calm down, calm down
My boyfriend is cheating on me
My mom did it again
Leaving it to a trash YouTuber
To our Elijah
What's wrong with everyone, really?
That's right
How can you be like Elijah?
Are you cheating on your girlfriend?
Fish oil~
Ugh, there are a lot of guys chasing me.
They all ran away after less than 6 months.
No, does this make sense?
What on earth is Elijah lacking?
I promise
Can I really trust you?
you today
You didn't eat anything.
Then I got into real trouble
Let's go, okay?
We need to go and eat something, let's go
Oh, it's okay, sister.
I haven't even had half a practice yet
Don't do that, okay?
sister
In this advance to the United States
The fate of our company is at stake.
How much money did you spend on the album?
It's still bearable
Why do you worry so much, all the time?
We'll go again
In the same industry
Let's not do this
I'm a lawyer too
child
The industry is difficult. What can I do?
Even among the same lawyers
I have to make a living
people who have been harmed by you
By recruiting
class damages lawsuit
Getting ready now
no personal feelings
I feel so bad too
Please save me
Judge David Kang
Oh, don't do this, okay?
Baby, why are you like this?
Is there anyone who really knows...
Oh, I'm feeling bad too?
What you ask me to do
I do what you ask me to do
I'll do anything, anything, anything, yeah
Hey, please save me just once
Please save me
Hey, I told you
What is there to do?
- Hey...
- But
There's one thing I'm curious about
yes
Ask, what…
ask, ask
tell me anything
He, Elijah's mother, CEO Cha
yes
Is this your first transaction?
Oh, yeah, whatever.
It's been quite a while since I did business.
At first
Information behind the entertainment industry
I did some collecting.
Oh…
Well then, Elijah.
After entering college?
Well, flies
I managed to keep them from catching up.
Wow, that's fun
Well, classically, it's like this
Stick to something like a gangster
Just, uh, Mr.
eh, eh, eh
That's tacky
- Is it tacky?
- Yes, yes.
So
neat
It's as simple as hiring a boy.
A boy?
To the guy following Elijah
show up and have
That's exactly what I'm saying
'Me and Elijah
Well, we're kind of like that, huh?'
'Stand back!'
'Don't mess around!'
kid, what
Do you believe that because you talk alone?
- I believe it.
- Huh?
Just wearing pajamas and snoring
If you show me a picture of Elijah, I will believe it.
No, sleep, pajamas picture that
Uh, where did I…
CEO Cha Jin-hee
They even gave you a picture to make you do it?
This time with this
Don't let the dung flies get caught
You know?
It's amazing, right?
원래 연예인 부모들
애 연예하는 거 질색팔색합니다
평생 끼고 살면서
꿀 빨아야 되는데
애먼 놈한테 뺏기면은
억울하잖아요
개새끼
예?
개새끼라고
저, 저요?
Where did I see it, but
Yes?
Please save me...
Sa-san, will you save me?
How about this?
Is it ambiguous?
Ah, it's a bit of a tough one.
Bring me some.
Yes, representative.
Are you the youngest?
Oh, you're good at your job?
thank you
Take your time and look around, Mr.
I know my tastes too
CEO
Now~
How is this child?
Fish oil~
Oh my god!
Okay, then let me...
Umm~
not you but you
Yes, representative.
Wow…
under…
Yes, Attorney Kang!
Yes, this is David Kang.
I thought about it a bit.
I guess what I'm saying is
I think that's right
What's going on?
yes?
I'm worried about Elijah.
Ha, that's right
It must be a huge shock.
Yeah
- Huh? Uh, uh!
- Uh, uh
Uh, hello
Hello~
Uh, uh
Wait…
No, Mr. Elijah, for some reason…
Wow~
The office is very spacious and nice, isn’t it?
Than you think
Uh…
uh…
uh? no way…
Oh, Mom, that’s…
Uh, what on earth did you do?
The kid called the head of the department
I didn't even know the child was gone
What on earth did you do?!
I heard you didn’t even come to work today!
Oh, mom, that's not it
Me, today Soyeon
I was just coming back from a trip to the hospital...
you…
ah…
Really, what should I do about this now?
Why don’t you find the kid quickly?
Oh, you left home?
The price right next to the apartment
It's my mom's house.
I can't do this anymore.
In this way
Then where are you staying?
Uh…
First of all, I have to stay in a hotel.
Until I find a house
More than that, a lawyer.
I don't know much about the law
This is simply
I don't think it's a problem between mother and daughter.
Right?
That's right
It's a problem between the artist and the agency.
yes
The agency deceives the artist
Interfering with and leaking private life
ridiculous
It's a breach of contract
Then
I signed an exclusive contract with my agency.
I want to cancel
Please file a lawsuit for me
Hey, who is this?
Case stolen by a high school graduate
Aren’t you lawyer Woo Myung-hoon?
Hey, who is this?
Even Elijah fans were mobilized
Intercepting someone else's case
Aren’t David Kang a high school graduate lawyer?
I didn't bother to explode again
You said you went to see CEO Cha?
Please let me take charge of this case
Do you want to lose to me that much?
Oh, my nose came out.
think what you want
- Come quickly.
- Yes
I guess it tastes good, right?
Your honor
The manuscript has already been certified
Notification of termination of exclusive contract has been completed.
between plaintiff and defendant
Judgment confirming the absence of an exclusive contract
I will save you
What is the reason for termination?
How many clauses are there in the contract?
Your honor
I still
Is it because I lack legal experience?
This is my first time seeing a contract like this.
Party A is the defendant, EK Entertainment.
Eul is an artist
This is Plaintiff Elijah.
However, as you can see, the contract
B's obligation is
One, two, three, four...
How many, how many?
There are more than twenty
‘Absolute obedience to agency instructions’
'No social media activity
'Diet control'
On the other hand, Party A’s obligations are
Not at all
zero
wow
You are absolutely perfect.
I read the manuscript and signed it.
Isn't it a contract?
Your own mother
They handed me a contract to sign.
While running the line
Do you have children who can read it carefully?
And right after graduating from high school?
If you are an adult
As long as the contract is signed
At least I have to take responsibility.
You understand, right?
But
On what basis?
Are you saying you are canceling the exclusive contract?
Mutual trust relationship is broken.
- Mmm
- Well…
That's it
contract
How many trillions and which paragraphs are there?
Whether it's written in the contract or not
Due to the nature of the exclusive contract
A relationship of mutual trust is essential
If it's broken
Cancellation is possible
It's a precedent
Ah, that
After working as a prosecutor for a long time,
You’ve forgotten a lot about civil law, right?
I understand
That plaintiff's attorney is
Now the plaintiff and defendant
Have you forgotten who we are?
Is that the question?
Does this sound like the answer?
I think you don't know
I'll answer you
mother and daughter
Oh, I see.
You didn't know
The breakdown of trust between mother and daughter
Now the plaintiff's attorney
Are you trying to break the heavenly law?
What did I do so wrong?
for my daughter
I just did my best
The representative expressly expresses the plaintiff’s free will.
You have never respected me
no
my precious daughter
I'm afraid I'll meet a bad guy
Are you worried?
I'm afraid I'll settle down and not dream bigger
What did you whip?
Is that wrong?
If so then
All parents in Korea are guilty!
Representative, representative to the plaintiff
dieting at an abnormal level
by request
physical and mental health
You are seriously violating
just
Due to the nature of the job shown,
I have to work harder than others
I just told you
Doing the same thing as others
Can you be more than others?
I am his biological mother.
A mother who deliberately destroys her daughter
Where is it?
Now, now, now
Now, calm down.
Now, manuscript
Please keep expressing your opinions
I can't help it
Your Honor, to the defendant
During the entire period of plaintiff's activity
Reveal your income and expenditure details
related accounting ledgers
so that you can submit
Please order
What!
Ugh
really
Do you want to go all the way to the end?
Now, the plaintiff
relevant grounds
Please submit in writing
Mr. Elijah
Are you okay?
You don't have to come to court in person.
I don't want to avoid it
It's my job
forward
It will get messier.
That's what a trial is like
I am prepared
Oh my! I'm fine
By the way
I'm taking a break from practice for the first time in 8 years.
The day is so long
alone all day
Being stuck in a hotel room
I'm so lonely
Mr. Elijah
There is an empty room in my house.
It's shabby, but would you like to come and stay?
Really?
Oh, I love it so much
But are you okay?
Sure, let's go together.
Oh, great!
Park Byun, that
Mr. Elijah is a part-time bakery server.
You're not planning on using it, are you?
Fans from all over the world come and bring it
Aiming for a big hit
Ah, Attorney Kang!
In everything, based on your own standards
Don't look at the world
Ah…
Oh, I guess you liked it?
Ah!
EK Entertainment, really, tsk, Mr.
No, income and expenditure data
He asked me to submit it
Even all kinds of useless things
I sent a lot!
Hahahaha!
Fuck this.
Haha, really…
Exclusive contract termination lawsuit
It's not easy to win
Boyfriend problem
What about the special nature of the mother-daughter relationship?
I'll go swimming
We need to look into the settlement issue.
If you find anything there
Because it's missing
What are you all doing?
Not ready to wake me up
Look at Attorney Jang.
Well, because it’s cramped.
Come here and do it
Ah…
The working environment is bad, really.
This guy’s public defense is really, ah…
It's not good
You can do it!
- Go for it!
- You can do it!
under…
“Joie de viva”
Hello…
Ah
hello
That
I decided to stay for a few days
Ah…
Once upon a time
I learned it while filming a movie.
But
I don't know if this is right
thank you
Oh, wait a minute.
Uh, it's okay, it's okay.
Child…
I said that because I was bored.
Can I do this?
I
I will never tell your sister.
- It's okay.
- Um...
Music sales revenue
The profits from the performance are huge.
no
There is so much profit
Get investment again?
To Elijah too
I don't know if the settlement would have been successful.
Did it work?
Too bad it wouldn't have happened
Huh?
- Attorney Jang
- Yes
Would you like to take a look at this?
These are overseas companies where funds flowed.
yes
Ah, the flow
- Is it too strange?
- under…
- It's not common.
- I smell it, I smell it.
Where do you not smell ramen?
No way, so shamefully alone…
under!
Isn't there a smell of distrust somewhere?
oh!
Wow, David Kang is the best!
I’m especially craving ramen today
- Wow
- I will eat well!
thank you!
I'll eat well
How far did you go? Hmm
Attorney Park is now
You showed me something
I think it would be good to take a look at this
That's right
witness
As the general manager of defendant EK Entertainment
You are in charge of finance and accounting, right?
yes, that's right
Elijah since last year
To raise funds for entering the United States
You promoted investment attraction.
yes, that's right
Mr. Elijah
Proceeds from music sales and performances
It must be significant.
Was additional external funding required?
The entertainment industry
I'm saying this because I don't know much.
- Um
- Global Artist
To raise one person
A huge amount of money is needed
Consulting for overseas expansion
Well, marketing, these costs alone...
is it so? These costs?
in LA
Halford & Brown Company
in new york
J.C Mackenzie
Huh?
How do I...
By the way
Of the money that flowed to this company
more than half
again flowed to a third company.
There was a trace
I went through a washing process here and there, but
The destination is
It's right there
Corporation headquartered in a tax haven
HOPE
Hope you like it?
hope
I don't know
What does that have to do with me?
In the end, you failed to attract investment.
What is the reason?
That's the investors' decision.
Why do you keep doing that to me...
Isn’t this fraudulent accounting?
Why did you fail to attract investment?
Your honor
Now the plaintiff's attorney
A groundless newspaper
I'm doing it
Is there any basis?
Oh, I'll submit it if you need it.
prepared by the investor's accounting team at the time.
This is a due diligence report.
‘EK Entertainment’s balance sheet is
It is not trustworthy'
‘Fund outflow confirmed’
Proceeds to be paid to the plaintiff
Did you steal it?
no!
That's all fabricated.
Ha, I'm sure
I have one more question.
submitted
In a truckload of papers
Who found it?
witness
Among my expenses was insurance premiums.
Wow, that's a lot of money
What is it about?
Even such details
How do you remember them all?
You probably remember them, right?
I tracked it down and found it was life insurance.
witness's sister
Elijah's Life Insurance
That is
Our company car... Huh!
At the company level
for artists
‘For artists’
Who is the beneficiary of the insurance?
If something happens to Elijah
The person who will receive the insurance money
Company funds flowed
One shareholder of Hope Co., Ltd.
This is the same person?
Soyeon Kim
seven years old
The only daughter of the witness
No!
This is all lies...
It's a false claim
Your honor
It's all just a vague guess.
Borrowed account in the name of a family member
Isn’t it possible to do it?
Plaintiff Representative
If it's going to be like this, it's better
File criminal charges for embezzlement
With unconfirmed evidence
Don't make malicious slander
Huh?
I will submit relevant evidence
Are you cheating on your mom?
stupid bastard
I told you not to be greedy!
Mom took a lot more
Why do you do this to me!
It doesn't matter if you do it or not
Why are you so greedy about the subject!
why?
Can't I be a little greedy?
what?
grandma!
Soyeon, why did you come out?
Is grandma here?
let's play with me
With grandma and dad
I have something to say, so go in.
Soyeon
I need to go outside
Let's go in quickly
Grandma…
Go quickly, the kid is coughing!
That guy really...
I prefer my baby to Elijah
I will raise you much better.
Do you know?
What he wants
I'll do everything so you won't be envious.
Everything is the best!
- Hello
- Huh? Mr. Wisdom
- Ah
- Mr. Elijah
Here, that
This is Jihye.
Ah…
hello
Elijah...
It's really Elijah Ma, right?
oh
Yes, that's right, Jihye unni.
Wow
Do you know my name?
I really, uh...
Wow, I'm not dreaming, am I?
Of course, Mr. Jihye.
Uh, my sister's song, uh
You're so nice, uh...
I’m looking forward to the next song too
Am I your sister?
Yeah
If you're cool, everyone will say it's your sister.
Okay then
What I prepared for our Jihye unnie
Let’s solve it, shall we?
gift…
- uh…
- Ta-da!
You know goods and ponies, right?
Uh, can I take this?
Of course I take it.
Wow
This is
T-shirt with my face on it
Wow, Elijah
thank you
Well, there are a lot, um…
You really gave me a lot, right?
Thank you, Elijah.
I'll go see it
Bye bye!
Ah
Let's go
Ha…
Jihye's sister and uncle
They intercepted it?
Insurance money for your parents’ death?
Yes, according to Attorney Jang.
to that uncle
It feels like I'm being abused...
how
To such a kind person...
It's called family
What is it?
Mr. Elijah
The settlement is not being done properly.
Did you really not know?
Mom was always like that
Mom will take care of it.
Don't worry about money
Just focus on music
You believed that?
You're my mom.
A person who wants me to do well more than anyone else
Did you believe it? Or
Is that what you wanted to believe?
Plaintiff Representative
Plaintiff's representative!
Ah, ah, yes
Ah, your honor.
Defendant's non-payment of settlement amount and
Details of embezzlement of music proceeds
to reveal
Director Kim Joo-won
I will sue you for embezzlement.
The deadline is pending the results of the investigation.
please estimate
Uh, plaintiff's attorney.
It’s been a while since I studied bar exam, so I learned criminal law.
Haven't you forgotten everything?
What do you mean by that?
Article 361 of the Criminal Code
Article 328 Paragraph 1
Relative mourning ceremony
Ah, this is the basic of basics.
The person who even became a judge... Haha
Property crime among family members
I can't punish you
Only if older brothers or sisters live together
What I can't punish
You didn't forget, right?
Siblings living separately can be punished
Does Kim Joo-won live with the plaintiff?
Try floating it
This is a family photo taken early last year.
the whole family
It was when we were living together
The plaintiff must have known
Didn't the plaintiff's attorney know?
um
Your honor
Plaintiff's claim
The case of fund leakage
When most people live in this house
Because it happened
Relative mourning rituals apply.
Even if I sued, it was immediately dismissed.
It's just a waste of time.
Ah…
If something happened during the period of cohabitation
I guess so.
Ah
The last one
It happened after I moved.
Why not sue me for even one of those things?
How much?
- It is 820,000 won.
- 820,000 won
Your honor
Well, when I lived in that house
It's true that it happened
But
The defendant's representative
Circumstances being overlooked
There is one thing
Kim Joo-won's daughter Kim So-yeon
Due to severe atopic dermatitis and allergic symptoms
Contact with the outside world as much as possible
must be avoided
So, Kim Joo-won
On the second floor where my family lives
Install a separate entrance door and thoroughly
Access to other family members
I've blocked it
Even the bathroom
We also have a separate living room
Of course, living expenses were also spent separately.
So to speak, on the second floor of the house owned by my mother.
It's like buying a lease for free.
We lived this together
Can we talk?
You really prepared a lot.
But
Me, your honor.
Our CEO Cha Jin-hee
He wants to say something.
Yes, say it
thank you
I did it all
Director Kim Joo-won
As the CEO, do as I tell you.
I just did it
- Ha…
- Fraud or embezzlement
So sue me
Elijah
Is this what you want?
sue my mom
Do you have any tissues?
toilet paper, toilet paper
Oh, by the way
My mother lives with me
Regardless of whether we live separately or not
Can be punished for being a direct blood relative
There are no more
I'm afraid you'll struggle in vain
This time again
Are you a direct blood relative?
yes
Are you in a situation where you have to sue your biological mother?
Are you giving up on your bet, Riverside?
What do you mean by that?
We are already from Baekseung
I took the case and won.
-And…
- I guess I'm mistaken.
not just one incident
To steal a client
These are the terms of your bet.
Customers who pay fees
Is it Elijah?
Not that kid
EK Entergo
That kid is penniless?
For a penniless kid
To the client who stole it from me
Start a fight?
Then why didn’t you stop it from the beginning?
Are you doing this now?
Do you think I'm so free?
- yes?
- Even such a minor incident.
Enough to take care of it?
I gave up on betting
quietly as promised
Is it okay to assume that the team is disbanding?
- Go outside.
- No, doctor.
Still
This is a lawsuit with a lot to gain if you win.
Suffering from abuse of power by the agency
Other star incidents
I can take over
yes
This is
you want to make
Is this the new O&Partners?
A disgrace to the people
A national law firm?
Or perhaps
Did you empathize too much?
I want to drive out my mother
From my daughter's point of view
What a disappointment.
I left it to you because I thought you looked like me.
I thought wrong.
Stop that lawsuit immediately.
The team is disbanded
Two desks No. 4
One size four and a half...
- Mr.
- Yes?
What are you doing now?
Ah, the desk in this room
They said take it all out?
yes?
- kid…
- Really?
Yes, really
Ha…
Lawyer Kang
Ji, ji, if this lawsuit is really filed, wow...
Will our team be disbanded?
In this damn company
I guess it’s not possible to represent Eul.
Me, that
Wow, I
Actually, it took a while from the beginning.
I don't think this is it
No, honestly this is
Well, it's not a public interest lawsuit, it's just nonsense.
Top stars are not socially underprivileged...
My mother, my brother, and my agency
It's an incredibly isolated situation.
Let's help these people
Wasn't it made public?
If I get fired here, I too will be a laid-off worker.
From my job
Is it a sin to want to protect it?
Am I the only one who is trash again?
I'm desperate too!
Junwoo
After…
What are you doing?
Do you really want to disband after this one incident?
If you quit
Seduce the nation's younger sister
sue my mom
We'll become a team that quits in the middle.
national trash team
you are the team leader
What should I do?
captain
Oh no
fuck
Ah…
Wisdom Sister
Shall we go in, Mr. Jihye?
Uh, be careful, oops.
Elijah Sister
Jihye is so sacred.
I'm worried about Elijah.
Let's go quickly
I bought strawberries, which is my sister’s favorite.
Even though the map is difficult
Sister!
ah…
sister
Uh…
Jihye, are you uncomfortable?
Shall we sit down for a moment?
- Let me see.
- Yes
Sister!
Mr. Jihye…
Ha, who…
Who did this?
Yeongsil hyung
What happened?
Didn't it work out? Jihye’s case?
under…
You can't punish me?
Ji-hye and uncle?
Only the assault part
I think I'll be punished with a soft bat.
Ji-hye embezzled her parents’ insurance money.
The investigation hasn't even started
He was indicted right away.
Because there is also civil affairs.
Please at least investigate
I begged like that, but...
under…
What kind of law is that?
If it's family
Are you saying it's okay to steal?
Uh, so the Constitutional Court
There was also someone who went to trial.
It was decided to be constitutional
About 10, 10 years ago
Ha…
Then now
Is there no way?
Me and Jihye?
That's it
Legally, yes.
Ha…
Is this correct?
You are lawyers.
Is everything right if it’s the law?
If it's family
Is it okay to do anything?
under…
That's not possible
Mr. Elijah
fact
I am the senior who runs away from home.
Before
Because I left home when I was in high school
Ah, ah…
Oh, well, I never said that.
That's a good story
My father had a big business.
had two wives
The problem is
My mom
It's the second time
brother
my father once a week
I used to come home
I guess you didn't like me at all
Whenever I see my father, I just
I stuttered
I was so nervous...
It's still like that now
If you're a little nervous
Like now
I stutter
Uh…
On that topic
What kind of lawyer is this, huh…
It's funny, right?
So
You didn't say anything?
Every time I stutter
My father was beaten harshly.
It has to be right to be fixed
Until I was in high school
every week
That's right
Well, I know for sure now
That…
That's
It was a crime
No more in the name of family
Crime should not be covered up
Lawyer Kang
we have to do something
long side
This time it's on a completely different level.
Relative mourning ceremony was held in 1953.
From the time the criminal law was enacted
This is a clause that existed
in 2012
The Constitutional Court has already
There has also been a decision on constitutionality.
National Sentiment Award
Uh, there might be a backlash.
-And…
- Please use me.
Yes?
There are people like Jihye in the world
How many are there?
That
I make a living thanks to the world's attention
You're a celebrity
By using me
People like Jihye
That there is
please tell the world
under the name of family
people being trampled
not protected by the law
There are people too
Mr. Elijah
family property crime
Gathering the victims
How about we all sue together?
I will cover all costs.
Of course, Jihye’s too.
um
I am grateful, but
That's not possible
- Yes?
- why?
That's
Because it's our job as public defenders.
Right, Attorney Kang?
If you mess up, the team will be disbanded.
The chances of winning are low
A fight with a high possibility of being criticized
Let's do it again?
yes
That's it
Because that's what Gongbyeon does.
Really everyone
Do you think the same?
Really?
a promise I made with my mom
I have to protect it
What should I do?
With fools who have no plan
I feel like I'm tied up
After…
Withdraw the lawsuit
You haven't done it yet?
Are you disobeying me now?
no way
‘I’m still the representative’
Are you doing this?
hmm…
Call a partner meeting
Let's discuss replacing the representative.
yes father
before that
Please take a look at this first.
What is this?
Created by secretary Seo who quit
This is a transcript.
my father
Regarding the appeal case of Chairman Jang Hyun-bae
It was about a phone call.
a branch of the Supreme Court
What are you doing!
What should you do?
Suspicion of trial transaction
It could be fatal to our firm.
Ha…
This transcript
When senior lawyers find out
I think there will be quite a stir.
Are you setting a trap?
under…
No way
Secretary Seo came to visit me.
Crying that it was unfair
You cut me off mercilessly that day.
in front of me
don't be funny
Probably bought it in advance
If I did that
I guess that's what my father taught me.
‘There is no human being without weaknesses in the world’
'If there is such a person'
‘Plant it’
'Weakness'
It's pretty good
yes
I'll watch you for a little while longer
your play house
Uh, Jeongin.
Let's go
Dr. Oh, did you convince me?
Ha, persuasion?
If you lose, it's over
You and me too
Huh? Lawyer Kang!
my life motto
‘The quality of the fight is
'Let's not even start in the first place'
Ha, it won't work this time.
Because of fools who have no solution
Attorney Kang, then…
Let's go, let's go
- Really?
- and!
Are we going to the Constitutional Court?
When should I go to the Constitutional Court now?
yes? So where do you want us to go?
I looked into it with the Constitutional Court.
About the funeral ceremony for relatives
There was a constitutional complaint filed.
It's been a while, but I don't think there's much progress.
Uh, I guess I wasn't getting any attention?
we
Let's get a lot of that attention.
For us
Because there is a star
Huh, no way!
Call for decision to be unconstitutional
Elijah Street concert?
Hey, that's a custom
Oh, then what is it?
Change the law?
If it’s the biggest stage…
It's Yeouido.
bingo
Let's go to the National Assembly
To change the wrong law
Ha…
yes!
let's go!
Well, if you don't want to
I fell out this time
I talked to Oh Jeong-in...
It's okay
Because it's a majority decision
I have to follow it, yeah
Junwoo Hwang
My job as a team member
I will do it
Attorney Kang too
please do your job
By all means
I want you to win
Well…
Popular singer Elijah
In the National Assembly audit
Adopted as a reference
It's becoming a big topic
Elijah received notice of attendance.
attend the National Assembly
Regarding the mother's suspicion of embezzlement
Whether to state it directly
I'm paying attention
Elijah recently
Biological mother and agency representative
With Cha Jin-hee
Due to a lawsuit confirming the non-existence of an exclusive contract
already once
for inter-family property crimes;
great interest
I have brought it up
Hey, the lawmakers are all excited now.
오랜만에 공중파 뉴스에
Because it’s a chance to get one shot
Oh, really?
Now at Yeouido beauty salon
Are you saying there aren't any empty seats?
Boy, unanimously.
I heard you were adopted as a reference?
Hey, in times like this, being a star is
It's good, right?
Hehehe
What is it?
why?
What's going on?
Hey
Look at this
What is it?
This is urgent breaking news.
Top star Elijah
Will I attend the National Assembly tomorrow?
While attracting national attention
Elijah's biological mother just now.
CEO Cha Jin-hee
emergency press conference
The news is that it has started
Woo Myung-hoon, this bastard…
Yeah, just
please insult me
I'm bad...
I'm a bad mom
CEO Cha Jin-hee’s
In the end, this desperate motherhood
It was the cause of all this trouble
What do you mean by that?
my daughter
You left me for a man
left home
And right away
filed a lawsuit against me
Mom
They accuse me of being an embezzler and a thief.
Oh my, I really want to die
Representative, please write this.
In these days
There is a saying that it is a South American bird.
If you look at the meaning
Bird crazy about men...
Well, that's what I mean, to put it nicely.
It's crazy, in love
Representative Cha in civil court
Admitted to all charges of embezzlement
Isn't it true?
Because of a family funeral
Although no investigation was conducted
Ha…
President, I can't help it.
About this part too
tell me the truth
Attorney, you are so cruel.
how can i use my mouth
You're asking me to talk about that.
Then let me tell you instead.
CEO Cha Jin-hee
No, before I was a representative.
Mother Cha Jin-hee
My son committed it alone
guilty of embezzlement
Instead, I'm going to turn it over
He made a false confession.
He said he did it all
What do you mean, all of a sudden?
mom
Mom, that’s not it, Mom…
Representative Cha!
I have a question, representative!
what…
Have you seen it?
This is what a mother is
All of the child's faults
A being who embraces my faults
That kind of being is
I'm a mom, by the way
Elijah, who was called the nation's daughter,
Sending a mother like this to jail...
It's shocking
How can you do that to your own mother?
But how can mom
Are you also getting rid of your grown daughter’s boyfriend?
I'm scared that my daughter will be like that too.
Not the nation's daughter
It's a national betrayal
After…
Elijah! Elijah!
Top star Elijah
After a while, at the National Assembly audit...
Every time you open your mouth, you talk nonsense
Withdraw!
Already in front of the National Assembly
Anti-fans and fans gather together
Exaggerate each other's opinions
The situations expressed
It is being produced
What is this Elijah really like?
It's Elijah!
Elijah!
Elijah! Elijah!
Wow, are you okay?
are you okay?
Brother, let's just go
Uh, after the press conference yesterday.
In the interest of fairness, Cha Jin-hee also
Adopted as reference, yes
Representatives from both sides were present, right?
yes
I, respected chairman
If you allow me
Before Elijah's statement
Just a word from our CEO Jinhee Cha.
Do you mind if I tell you something?
Uh, sure.
thank you
yes, thank you
Ah, dear lawmakers.
This foolish mother
Just one thing
A shameless request
I'll upload it
Yes, my daughter was young.
Ugh, yelling and getting angry.
Because of dad
in similar situations
Well, the trauma is very severe.
It's a serious position.
Please ask as gently as possible.
I beg you to please
Umm
Well, even in this situation
You're worried about your daughter.
Uh, yes
Because I'm a mom
Diarrhea child
stab my heart
Even if everything is stolen
child's path
I hope you don't stumble and fall
It's my mother's heart
- Ha…
- Yes, I will keep that in mind.
Uh, the lawmakers too.
Please be especially careful.
- Yes
- Yes, then.
Hey Elijah
Please stand on the witness stand.
Yes, Chairman.
Mr. Elijah
I will call you a reference.
Yes, Senator.
Did you see the press conference yesterday?
- Yes
- Is this true?
Press conference details
some of it is true
Some are not true
So which part is true?
When I was young
My father only drinks
without reason
I used to beat up the house and destroy it.
Every time that happens, my mom
Hug us with your whole body
I used to protect
and for us
divorced my father
You've had a hard time
it's all true
I, respected Congressman Kim Jun-pyo
To Elijah Reference
Could you please ask me one thing?
Let's ask directly
Ah, thank you
reference person
- Yes
- Currently in the Constitutional Court
Provisions for funeral rites for relatives
The constitutional petition is in progress.
You know, right?
yes
Why did the reference come here?
By forming public opinion
In the constitutional petition trial
To make an impact, right?
yes, that's right
Then the reference person ends up
so hard
The mother who raised me
to be punished criminally
Are you even trying to change the law?
Is that correct?
yes, that's right
That's it.
Oh, thank you, Senator.
In my opinion, rather
Why is there a provision for funeral rites for relatives?
Should I have it?
Between parents and children
You can't sue or file a complaint due to property issues.
There must be a limit
Proof that families are maintained
I think the reference shows it.
Isn't that right, reference?
Reference person?
Oh, congressman, uh
Elijah's representative
This is Kang David
May I tell you something?
Let me tell you.
thank you
CEO Cha Jin-hee
My daughter
What a smart and ambitious person you are.
You know it well, right?
Why did your daughter stay like that for so long?
I follow everything my mom tells me to do.
Contract or anything
Sign everything that is handed to you
Whether the settlement is done properly or not
Didn't you even ask or question?
Don't you know?
What are you talking about now?
Really your daughter
Could it be that he didn't know anything?
me here
Do I have to answer?
Only what you can do
You can do it.
Do you really think you didn't know?
Mr. Elijah
Even though I knew it all this time
You endured it, right?
The person who protected the reference when he was young
Because of my gratitude to my mother
Even though I know everything
Didn’t you endure it?
Right?
No matter how much you try to hide it, the truth is
It's bound to be revealed
reference person
Sincerely
worried about
Because there are people
Even within EK Entertainment
Sincerely, CEO Cha
There are a lot of people worried
Did you know?
About the extraordinary love of luxury goods and the tendency to waste
Um, uh…
what to say now
Are you doing it?
sacred…
Uh, it's the National Assembly.
On what basis are you making this one-sided claim...
Elijah stole money
Seongsu-dong apartment purchased
Whose name is it in now?
Uh, wait a minute, uh…
Oh wait, now
What are you talking about?
No, it's like this because he's a lawyer.
Can I just say anything?
Uh, Cha Jin-hee’s reference.
Yes, calm down.
agent for both sides
Are you here to fight?
This is a place to explain, listen, and ask questions.
Please be careful
Yes, now, agent.
- Please continue.
- Chairman
The main reference person
There's one more person here.
Can I come in?
uh…
Permission, please come in.
- Thank you, Hwang Byeon.
- Reference…
No, but
Is it okay to do something like that?
No, I can't...
not you but you
Ah, Chairman.
May I stand on the witness stand for a moment?
yes
Mr. Elijah
Minha Kang
A luxury store in Cheongdam-dong
VIP dedicated staff
Is that correct?
yes, that's right
The apartment I live in now
Who bought it for me?
Can you please answer?
yes
sitting here
This is CEO Cha Jin-hee.
Ah…
ah…
Oh, excuse me, but do you have a corporate card?
Can I take a look?
yes
Wow, Black, Wow!
Hey~ this
Which company's card is this?
I heard the limit is very high?
This is the card of the CEO of EK Entertainment.
Oh my, this
What about this, this, this?
Boy, the embezzlement of corporate funds is
Doesn’t this apply to funerals for relatives?
no
It's a lie
I don't even remember that.
I don't even know who that person is!
Ah, yes
To someone I don't know
You are generous enough to give like this.
You were a very generous person.
Okay
Minha Kang
Representative Cha
Why did you do these things?
ah…
under…
Well, I'm embarrassed
You said you liked me
Now, now, now
Things you don't even know how to thank your mom for
Mom made us all stars.
A girl who is nothing
I thought it was good because I was doing well.
Ha…
Now I'm going to live just for myself
With you
Have fun
Chairman
In these days
There is a saying that it is a South American bird.
Yes, yes, yes? Me, me, South America?
crazy about men
Well, that's what I'm saying
To put it nicely, it's crazy.
- in love
- David Kang, that crazy…
Minha Kang
It must have been a difficult decision.
Dealing with such a large supplier... no
sorry
Against this very grateful person
I decided to reveal the truth
How did you do it?
yes?
No, that's right, the lawyer
As an accomplice to business embezzlement, well...
Hahahahaha!
haha…
Isn’t there something else besides that?
Ah~
kid, that
What the representative did for me
the apartment
Now that I know that
It was a tin can house.
I set up collateral, so it's just a shell.
No, it's manipulation.
Hey! Who are you? What the heck
You say you don’t know, witness!
If you commit perjury, you will be punished for perjury...
Hey, CEO!
I really believed in the CEO.
No, but
Well, what is the real deal?
Well, I handed it over to Ace.
- No, how can a person...
- This is an insult, Chairman!
How does love change?
Oh, calm down!
Calm down!
this is not a court
agent for both sides
Do that much
Uh, let's take a break and then we'll continue.
Elijah, drink some water.
Good job, lawyer.
From now on
What I really wanted to say
Because the board is all set
yes
Attorney Jang!
Mr. Elijah
Uh, Elijah.
Are you here, Jihye?
Thank you, lawyer.
Oh, what is it?
Mr. Elijah
- Fighting
Fighting.
Mom and I
Why did it end up like this?
I had such a good mom when I was young.
Ha…
Was money the problem?
Maybe so
Our family forever
Money I've never even touched
As it started pouring in
all these things
I think it's started
I honestly
About this with my mom
I didn't want to fight until the end
Money?
Even if you give everything to mom,
It didn't matter
I just
wanted freedom
I spent my whole life using my mom’s ATM machine.
Because I didn't want to live
If you just cancel the exclusive contract somehow,
I was thinking of leaving
But
Hey, Elijah
While meeting Jihye over there,
'This isn't just me'
I found out
over there
Ji-hye's uncle and aunt
Even after embezzling my nephew's disability pension,
Make money by begging
I threw my nephew out on the street.
If the income is not good
I was whipped
sadly sometimes
family is closest
He is also a perpetrator
I am the perpetrator now...
Wait, yes
for a moment
Could you please stand up?
Mr. Wisdom
These people here
with my fan club
With the help of public interest lawyers
brought to this place
family property crime
These are the victims.
The wealth accumulated throughout one's life
An old man who was stolen by his child
Mom's legacy
Boy stolen by stepfather
I am a disabled person with limited mobility.
My brother is stealing my property
The one who couldn't stop it
I've been so embarrassed
Although I received a lot of love undeservedly
take full responsibility for it
I couldn't finish it
I just
Because everyone is interested and watching
I am a person who exists
The way I repay you is
I became a tool
not yet receiving attention
But we need to know
about someone's pain
I think it's a matter of informing
please help
The pain of these people
Law and family
does not protect
The injustice of these people
Mr. Elijah
Uh…
Still, the family funeral ceremony
Uh, since ancient Rome.
The law does not cross the threshold
So much so that there is a saying
It is also a very old custom.
Even in our country, uh
Over 70 years since it was enacted
It's a law that doesn't change
Legal stability too
As much as concrete validity, maybe
It's a more important value than that.
Yes, you are correct.
legal stability
It's an important value
By the way, Chairman
For over 70 years
What hasn't changed is
someone
have been suffering
Could this be what it means?
If the law does not cross the threshold
Inside that door
cruel
A lawless zone unfolds
Dear lawmakers,
law
As times change, it must change.
The law is not a fossil trapped in the past
Living and breathing with the times
so that it can become the norm
Bringing life to the National Assembly
I think it is a noble mission.
Representatives
Please
wise judgment
Lawyer
Rice, lawyer, over there.
Lawyer!
Wow
Hey, what should I do?
Talk to the prosecutor...
Why do you keep touching me?
why?
Are you saying it’s good for me too?
No, lawyer!
jeon!
He doesn't tell me 100%
I don't take care of clients.
Get a new lawyer
No, there
No, lawyer.
No, no, lawyer!
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Ah, hey!
- Ugh!
- Ugh, I’m surprised, why? again
I really hate to admit this, but
Ah
You were great today, Attorney Kang.
Ha! What, what, what, what
Hey, ha! kid, what
Ah, well, it's really true once again
Kid, what, what am I, what
When was it not cool?
Again, showing off again
I'm afraid I'll be like this...
No, but what happens?
Can you win?
I don't know
You might lose
But I mean
Even if you lose, use today’s defeat as a stepping stone
What about the world?
I'll take another half step forward
Next time someone
there again
You'll be able to start anew
Lawyer Kang
Wow! Hey, this is
As I said, it was kind of cool.
Admit it? admit?
Hwang Jun-woo, isn’t it?
Ah, of course
Until just now
I couldn't get used to it
Now it's just that
You sound like Attorney Kang.
- What?
- 'Even if I lose'
‘Today’s victory’
- ‘Foot, stepping stone’…
- Okay, that's enough.
- Yoo Byeon, call me oppa from tomorrow.
- Why?
If you’re cool, aren’t you my brother?
- yes? Why me?
- 'Even if I lose'
If you're cool, call me your brother!
- ‘Today’s victory’…
- I didn't say oppa!
'This incident'
‘The provisions for funeral rites for relatives’
‘uniformly’
‘Excessively broad scope’
‘About property crimes committed by relatives’
‘Regardless of the severity’
‘I’m trying to get the sentence waived’
'Being in a vulnerable position within the family
'For members'
'Tolerating economic exploitation'
'There is a risk of consequences'
'Ie'
'Constitutional Judge
'With unanimous opinion'
‘I decide as follows’
'Order'
'Criminal law'
‘Article 328, Paragraph 1’
‘It does not comply with the Constitution’
Ha…
wow!
Today at the Constitutional Court
Provisions for funeral rites for relatives
A decision that is historically inconsistent with the Constitution
It was taken down
Now it was a blind spot of the law.
About property crimes committed by family members
eligible for legal protection
The road is open
Uh, I'm the representative here, representative!
- Let's go.
- Fish oil!
Oh my, Elijah
- Elijah, wait a minute.
- Wow
- Mom was wrong, huh?
- Go.
mom was wrong
You know, it's all a mistake!
mom
- Now, now, now, wait a minute.
- Ah...
Uh, Elijah
give birth to me
For raising me all this time
thank you
Uh, yeah
Uh, our good Elijah.
Then I'll drop the complaint.
- Our people...
- But mom
I'm fired now
get out of my life
- Come on, let's go quickly.
- Let's go.
Hey, I
how did i raise you
- Stop it!
- Hey, you
You will be punished, hey!
It's your mom who made you a star!
I…
Is this the pro bono team?
yes, that's right
Who are you?
Uh, Justice Victims Solidarity.
I came here as an introduction
Here's my case
I heard you would take care of it
Oh, yes, I got it.
due to a wrong trial
You lost your father...
yes
The judge in charge abused his power
With a rigged trial
made my father die
The name of the judge in charge...
This is Kang David
Attorney Gippeum Park
For the past 10 years I
These are the things I collected
Trust the evidence
I don't mind going to hell
David Kang, his hypocrisy
If you can reveal it
That human and me
There is a deep relationship
Jaebeom Yoo?
His father is the owner of the company?
the defendant
I changed it, Attorney Kang.
Come catch Yoo Man-man.
Otherwise I can’t do it.
It's a rigged trial...
How is it going?
Chairman Jang Hyun-bae's case
Are you saying this is a rigged trial?
David Kang, this man
Is this sane?
I'll take care of it
Let's step down
-Why don’t you take on that case?
- How can we...
When a victim of a powerful crime comes to visit
Isn’t it your job to help?
Are you really going to take my case?
Everyone says they will do it?
Please tell me everything